[
  {
    "front": "Ensolarado (‚òÄÔ∏è)",
    "back": "zonnig",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Preocupar-se (ü§î)",
    "back": "zorgen",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Deveremos, vamos (‚û°Ô∏è)",
    "back": "zullen",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "terminar, completar",
    "back": "afmaken",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.802Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "exceto, al√©m de",
    "back": "behalve",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.802Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "promessa",
    "back": "belofte",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "embaixo, inferior",
    "back": "beneden",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "gasolina",
    "back": "benzine",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "famoso, renomado",
    "back": "beroemd",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "pagar",
    "back": "betalen",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "mover-se, mexer",
    "back": "bewegen",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "nublado",
    "back": "bewolkt",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "ficar, permanecer",
    "back": "blijven",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "queimar",
    "back": "branden",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "trazer, levar",
    "back": "brengen",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "vizinho (homem)",
    "back": "buurman",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Exato ou correto (‚úÖ)",
    "back": "correct",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Filha (üëß)",
    "back": "dochter",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Girar, rodar (üîÑ)",
    "back": "draaien",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Flutuar (üõ∂)",
    "back": "drijven",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  }
]